好吧 这个我一点也笑不出来
Yeah, this is not making me laugh at all.
那这个等成熟了再给你说
We'll bring that one back when it's ready.
好了 有天消防安全员问我...
Okay, fire safety guy asked me the other day,
然后你就换成自己的语气 我在床上抽烟吗?
and this is your voice... do I smoke in bed?
然后我就说 我从来都没什么好抱怨的
And I said, 'I've never had any complaints.'
口味太重了? 太重了?
Too shock? Too shock?
好吧 这还有一个半成品的想法
Okay, this is kind of a half an idea.
这个情景是如果你是一位消防员
All right, so the idea is if you're a fireman
要把湿毯子铺到什么东西上...
putting a wet blanket on something...
你迟到了 是的 而且我非常非常抱歉
- You are late. - Yes, and I am incredibly sorry.
我昨晚不是在家睡的 我就是...睡过头了
I was not in my own apartment last night. I just... I overslept.
好吧 迟到之后说你中风什么的还行
Okay, having a massive stroke is an excuse for coming in late to this office.